<behaviour Name="RACOON" defaultMood="NEUTRAL">
  <speeches>
    <speech id="0">
      <statements>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text> I have an assignment due tomorrow. You know what it’s about? Freakin’ Aristotle.</text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>MAD</moodChange>
          <text>He is such a tool, you know that? I’m tired of this fetishization of greek philosophers like they’re these infallible perfect demi-gods, they’re all dumb self righteous jerks.</text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>SAD</moodChange>
          <text>
            Why did I even start studying philosophy? Maybe I should drop out.
            But my student debt is already building up, so it would probably be bad. I hate this.
          </text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>I'm itching so hard for a cup right now. I’ve been up all night researching Aristotle, who’s is really creepy by the way, in case you were wondering, and I’m so tired I literally can’t think of anything except how terrible he is and how college is equally terrible.</text>
          <choice>
            <option result="1">You should drop out, this doesn’t sound good for you.</option>
            <option result="2">Stay in school. It's only temorary.</option>
          </choice>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
    <speech id="1">
      <statements>
        <entry>
          <text> Yeah… You’re probably right. I just hate making decisions. I always procrastinate it until the last moment, and end up winging it. We’ll see how it goes.</text>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
    <speech id="2">
      <statements>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>Maybe. Everything is temporary. So… why bother at all? Nothing really matters anyways, does it? .</text>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
    <speech>
      <statements>
        <!-- Hver entry her er ment å tilsvare en "snakkeboble"-->
        <entry>
          <moodChange>MAD</moodChange>
          <text> I flunked the Aristotle essay. Apparently I was «too biased» and «passive-agressive» and «not fulfilling the basic criteria of an academic essay». </text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>But… That kind of made me relieved. Because now I have more reason to drop out. Because I’m not even good at it, so why force myself through it? It just makes me miserable. </text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>I think it’s time to do something new, that… It doesn’t have to be important, or make me rich, or whatever. I want to do something because I can, something that’s my choice.  Instead of just following the flow.</text>
          <choice>
            <option result="3">You should find a job, if you’re dropping out. Do something you’ve been curious about!</option>
            <option result="4">You really shouldn’t drop out. Don’t end up like me.</option>
          </choice>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
    <speech id="3">
      <statements>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>Yeah. There’s almost too much to chose from. But I’m kind of looking forward to it.</text>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
    <speech id="4">
      <text>What’s wrong with ending up like you? You’re good at what you do. People want you around. Can’t really say the same for me. Thanks for the coffee.</text>
    </speech>
    <speech id="5">
      <statements>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>SAD</moodChange>
          <text>Hey. You… Do you know if the manager is in…? If I could… I have something to uh, give them. Don’t look at me like that. I need a job. I dropped out last week, and I need some way to survive. </text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <moodChange>NEUTRAL</moodChange>
          <text>And… besides, you make it look kind of fun. To make coffee. And talking to people.</text>
        </entry>
        <entry>
          <text>Well, uh, if you see the manager could you give them this? …Okay, I’m leaving. Thanks for the help and uh, the coffee. See you around.</text>
        </entry>
      </statements>
    </speech>
  </speeches>
</behaviour>
